[
  {
    "text": "q. How do you comfort a JavaScript bug? a. You console it.",
    "question": "How do you comfort a JavaScript bug?",
    "answer": "You console it.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/06/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the child component have such great self-esteem? a. Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
    "question": "Why did the child component have such great self-esteem?",
    "answer": "Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "05/22/2017",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards? a. Because they use a strongly typed language!",
    "question": "Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards",
    "answer": "Because they use a strongly typed language",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/23/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript", "java", "c#"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the functional component feel lost? a. Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
    "question": "Why did the functional component feel lost?",
    "answer": "Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "05/22/2017",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why was the JavaScript developer sad? a. Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
    "question": "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/10/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript", "node"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the developer go broke? a. Because he used up all his cache!",
    "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
    "answer": "Because he used up all his cache!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/17/2013",
    "tags": [],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the React Higher Order Component give up? a. Because it sur-rendered to the prop-aganda!",
    "question": "Why did the React Higher Order Component give up?",
    "answer": "Because it sur-rendered to the prop-aganda!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "10/31/2017",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "When a JavaScript date has gone bad, \"Don't call me, I'll callback you. I promise!\"",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/09/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 2
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the react class component feel relieved? a. Because it was now off the hook.",
    "question": "Why did the react class component feel relieved?",
    "answer": "Because it was now off the hook.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 4
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the react developer have an addiction? a. Because they were completely hooked on the hooks proposal.",
    "question": "Why did the react developer have an addiction?",
    "answer": "Because they were completely hooked on the hooks proposal.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 4
  },
  {
    "text": "q. What does a React proposal mean? a. It means to swallow something hook, line and sinker.",
    "question": "What does a React proposal mean?",
    "answer": "It means to swallow something hook, line and sinker.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why was the react developer late to everything? a. Because they were playing hooky with the hooks proposal",
    "question": "Why was the react developer late to everything?",
    "answer": "Because they were playing hooky with the hooks proposal.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why couldn’t the React component understand the joke? a. Because it didn’t get the context.",
    "question": "Why couldn’t the React component understand the joke?",
    "answer": "Because it didn’t get the context.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "tags": ["javascript", "react"],
    "rating": 2
  },
  {
    "text": "Dev1 saw a strange JavaScript function & asked, \"What is this?\". Dev2 responded, \"I don't know. I would've called you, but I was in a bind\"",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/09/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 3
  },
  {
    "text": "Two JavaScript developers walked into the variable `bar`. Ouch!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/10/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 3
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap? a. Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request.",
    "question": "Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap?",
    "answer": "Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/11/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks? a. Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
    "question": "Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks?",
    "answer": "Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/12/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 4
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost? a. Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
    "question": "Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost?",
    "answer": "Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/13/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript", "coffeescript"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. What do you call __proto__? a. Dunder proto q. Michael Scott was the regional manager where? a. __mifflin__",
    "question": "What do you call __proto__? Dunder proto. Michael Scott was the regional manager where?",
    "answer": "__mifflin__",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/16/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript"],
    "rating": 3
  },
  {
    "text": "q. How did the doctor revive the developer? a. The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
    "question": "How did the doctor revive the developer?",
    "answer": "The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/16/2013",
    "tags": ["css"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the C# developer fall asleep? a. Because he didn't like Java.",
    "question": "Why did the C# developer fall asleep?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't like Java.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/18/2013",
    "tags": ["java", "c#"],
    "rating": 2
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor? a. Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
    "question": "Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor?",
    "answer": "Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/19/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript", "knockout", "backbone"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings? a. Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
    "question": "How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings?",
    "answer": "Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/20/2013",
    "tags": ["css"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why was Ember.js turning red? a. Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
    "question": "Why was Ember.js turning red?",
    "answer": "Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/24/2013",
    "tags": ["javascript", "ember"],
    "rating": 5
  },
  {
    "text": "dev1 > What tool do you use to switch versions of node? dev1> nvm, I figured it out.",
    "question": "dev1 > What tool do you use to switch versions of node?",
    "answer": "dev1> nvm, I figured it out.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "08/30/2019",
    "tags": ["javascript", "node"],
    "rating": 1
  },
  {
    "text": "q. Why did the Web A11y Dev keep getting distracted? a. Beacuse they couldn't maintain focus!",
    "question": "Why did the Web A11y Dev keep getting distracted?",
    "answer": "Beacuse they couldn't maintain focus!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/19/2019",
    "tags": ["javascript", "css"],
    "rating": 2
  },
  {
    "text": "q. How do you make a Web App accessible? a. ARIA kidding me?",
    "question": "How do you make a Web App accessible?",
    "answer": "ARIA kidding me?",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/19/2019",
    "tags": ["javascript", "css"],
    "rating": 1
  }
]
